{
    "subject": "resource/Jo_Van_Fleet",
    "predicate": "ontology/deathYear",
    "object": "1996",
    "human_readable": "Jo Van Fleet died in 1996.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.8497682809829712,
            "question": "When did Jo Van Fleet die?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5914080739021301,
            "question": "What year was Jo Van Fleet born in?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.34211093187332153,
            "question": "Was Jo Van Fleet a famous actor?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.30787596106529236,
            "question": "What was Jo Van Fleet's nationality?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.26814910769462585,
            "question": "Was Jo Van Fleet involved in theater productions?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.26377493143081665,
            "question": "In what films or television shows did Jo Van Fleet appear?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.2148752063512802,
            "question": "Did Jo Van Fleet win any awards for her acting?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.20699478685855865,
            "question": "Is there a biographical film or documentary about Jo Van Fleet?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.1613963097333908,
            "question": "Did Jo Van Fleet have any notable relationships with other actors or directors?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.16115707159042358,
            "question": "What were some of the defining roles of Jo Van Fleet's career?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Jo Van Fleet died in 1996.",
            "html": "dbpedia_2473_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Did Jo Van Fleet have any notable relationships with other actors or directors?",
            "html": "dbpedia_2473_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Is there a biographical film or documentary about Jo Van Fleet?",
            "html": "dbpedia_2473_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Did Jo Van Fleet win any awards for her acting?",
            "html": "dbpedia_2473_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2473_12.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2473_14.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2473_2.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2473_26.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2473_4.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2473_41.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2473_49.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2473_50.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2473_68.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2473_76.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Based on the context information, I can evaluate the triple \"Jo Van Fleet died in 1996\" as follows:\n\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n\nThis is because all five documents mention that Jo Van Fleet died on June 10, 1996. Therefore, the information supports the triple and the answer should be \"yes\"."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```"
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "The Least Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}